(This drama is related to specific characters, institutions, and groups It has nothing to do with the case and is purely fictitious (I hereby inform you)
(本剧与特定人物 机构 团体 案件无关 纯属虚构 特此告知)
(Episode 8)
(第8集)
Big brother
大哥
Go quickly...
快走…
safe code
保险箱密码
Damn it
该死
Yongbi
永弼
Let me go first before talking
先放开我再说
why are you doing this to me
你为什么要这样对我
Then why did brother do this to me?
那大哥为什么要这样对我
What's wrong with me
我怎么了
He didn't even mention anything about his career to me.
都更事业的事对我只字不提
You want me to sell drugs to provide you with funds?
还要我卖毒品提供你资金
But he threw me off the cliff again
却又把我扔下悬崖
Brother, we can do this Is it related to liver and gallbladder photography?
大哥 我们这样也算 肝胆相照的关系吗
Who told you that?
是谁那么告诉你的
Something about Togen's career I plan to tell you later
有关都更事业的事 我打算之后才要跟你说
what's your reason
你有什么理由
Only tell your successor later
要之后才跟接班人说
Because... it's really...
因为… 真是…
The correct answer is…
正确答案是…
Because you want to monopolize
因为你想独吞
What is the password
密码是多少
There are only three chances
机会只有三次
Password…
密码…
It's your death anniversary, asshole
是你的忌日 混蛋
Are you satisfied?
满意了没
Damn it
该死
catch him
抓住他
let me go...
放开我…
I only ask once
我只问一次
What is the password
密码是多少
7777 brat
7777 臭小子
What a lucky set of numbers
真是幸运的一组数字
Also thinking about old friendship
也是 念在旧情
I'll spare your life
我就饶你一命吧
Big brother…
大哥…
money
钱
where is my money
我的钱呢
where is the money
钱在哪里
Silly boy
傻小子
Who puts cash in a safe these days?
现在谁会把现金放在保险箱里
It's all in the bank, you brat.
都嘛存在银行里 臭小子
Brother, I know you don’t like banks
大哥 我知道你不喜欢银行
where is the cash
现金在哪里
I mean seriously, it's in the bank.
我是说真的 存在银行里了
Let's change my wrist this time
这次换手腕吧
Yongbi
永弼
Although the sneak attack was successful
虽然偷袭成功
But he kept resisting
但他一直反抗
It's a bit laborious
有点费力呢
Thank you for your hard work
辛苦了
Big brother, your love has learned from Jiang Dou
大哥 你的爱将斗学来了
I'll ask you one last time
我最后再问你一次
where is the cash
现金在哪里
Brother has no cash on him, brat
大哥身上没有现金 臭小子
Because I asked him to deposit it in the bank, which is safer
因为我请他存在银行 比较安全
You guy...
你这家伙…
where is the cash
现金在哪里
Hey you guy
喂 你这家伙
Big brother
大哥
Am I your dog...
我是你的狗吗…
Because I'm the boss
因为我是老大
Not yet
现在还不行
Have to wait a while longer
还要再等一段时间
what
什么
What are you doing?
愣着做什么
sit down
坐下
Come
来
If you want me to sit down, do I have to sit down?
你要我坐下 我就得坐下吗
If I act one more time, I will be beaten.
再多演一下 我都要被打了
How about my acting skills?
怎么样 我演技不错吧
What is going on? What is going on?
这是什么情况 这是怎么回事
Dou Xue said no
斗学说不行
It means it's not possible yet
意思是现在还不行
Thoughts about fighting...
斗学的想法…
same as you
跟你一样
Let's seize it and plan a career.
我们抢下都更计划事业吧
Really, then why are you rejecting me?
真是的 那为什么还拒绝我
If Dou Xue takes action in person
斗学如果亲自出马
It will be difficult to gain recognition on the road
在道上会很难得到认可
From now on, my little brother will rebel Douxue has nothing to say
以后小弟要造反 斗学也无话可说
Of course, they all plan their careers more It won't fall into his hands
当然都更计划事业 也不会落到他手上
So
所以啊
What I mean is…
我的意思是…
To borrow someone else's knife
要借别人的刀
Yeah, it's a tactic of killing someone with a borrowed knife.
是啊 借刀杀人之计
Killing with a Borrowed Knife
借刀杀人之计
what does that mean
那是什么意思
We need to find a substitute to kill for us.
得找个替我们杀人的替身
like a stuntman
像替身演员那样
Yeah
嗯
By the way, there’s also…
对了 还有…
I want to ask you something
要拜托你一件事
That’s right…
没错…
what what happened
什么 什么事
You don't need to know
你不用知道啦
It's okay. Come and have a drink.
没事 来 喝一杯
What? What do you want to ask me for?
什么啊 要拜托我什么
I'll tell you later
之后再跟你说
Damn it
该死
Yongbi
永弼
It hurts, brat.
很痛 臭小子
Come here, you all, come here
过来 你们都过来
Wait...
等等…
Hello Yongbi
喂 永弼
you are really over
你真的结束了
The soup rice you like so much What should I do if I can’t eat anymore?
你那么喜欢的汤饭 以后吃不到了 怎么办
Bastard
混蛋
Okay, don't move at all.
好了 通通都别动
Why don't you come sooner and you're here now?
你怎么不快点来 现在才来
The timing is just right
时机刚好啊
What's wrong
怎么了
Brother
哥
Brother, are you okay?
哥 你没事吧
Big brother…
大哥…
Douxue…
斗学…
Brother, are you okay?
大哥 你没事吧
Brother, are you having a brain problem?
哥 你是不是脑子有问题
Aren't you crazy?
你没疯吗
Yeah
嗯
A gangster is not a fool
流氓又不是傻瓜
I'm a prosecutor
我是检察官
Will the gangster believe my words?
流氓会相信我的话吗
Find a way to make him believe it
要想办法让他相信
So…
所以…
You want me to help instigate Liu Yongbi Let him kill Lian Guangzhuo
你要我帮忙煽动柳永弼 让他干掉廉光卓
You can take the opportunity to rise to the top and become the real boss.
你再趁机上位成为真正的老大
You will also catch big fish
你也会因为抓到大鱼
Become a star prosecutor
成为明星检察官
Oh my God, you want me to do this Do you want me to be a prosecutor?
天啊 你是为了要我做这种事 才要我当检察官吗
Otherwise it's because I like you Do you want to see you succeed?
不然是因为我喜欢你 想看你出人头地吗
good
好
How could Li Douxue be someone else's younger brother?
李斗学怎么可能当别人的小弟
Okay, you just become a national gangster
好 你就当个让全国黑道分子
The boss who gets scared when he hears his name
听到名字就闻风丧胆的老大
Being a bad guy
当坏人里面
The worst kind of bad guy
最坏的那种坏人
But…
不过…
I'll help you this time...
我这次帮完你…
I don’t need to owe you any more favors.
就不用再欠你人情了吧
I helped you get rid of the murder charge and go to jail.
我帮你顶下了杀人罪去坐牢
Life is ruined It would be too easy to just write it off like this.
一辈子被毁了 就这样一笔勾销太容易了吧
Help you become the boss of the country
帮你当上全国老大
Is this compensation enough?
这样的补偿够了吧
Okay. If the result is good, then so be it.
好 结果是好的话就那样吧
That's not possessiveness
那不是占有欲
My heart towards Dingchen
我对定辰的心
Not possessive
不是占有欲
If I were really that possessive
我如果真的那么有占有欲
Don't care about any favors I would have arrested you and locked you up a long time ago
才不管什么人情 早就把你抓去关了
Really?
是吗
It seems I have to be careful
看来我得小心点
Otherwise, Prosecutor Choi might handcuff me.
不然崔检察官可能会把我上铐
But…
不过…
Let's do this first thing
先做好这次的事吧
You boy
你这小子
play again
再玩一下
And…
还有…
I have one more thing to ask you
我还有一件事要拜托你
Big brother
大哥
The recording is not over yet
录音还没结束
Because during the demolition process
因为在拆迁过程中
Too many people were injured
有太多民众受伤
Attracted media attention
引发了媒体的关注
We need a scapegoat
我们需要找个代罪羔羊
The higher ups hope so too
上头也希望那样
Li Douxue
李斗学
Let him take the responsibility for violent demolition
让他扛下暴力拆迁的责任
Send him to jail
送他去坐牢吧
Do you want to learn?
斗学吗
Why, he is your right-hand man So no?
怎么 他是你的左右手 所以不行吗
No
没有
I will do as you ask
我会照您的吩咐做
Anyway, I plan to...
反正我也打算…
Find an opportunity to deal with him
找机会处理掉他
boss
老板
We really get along
我们真聊得来
thank you
谢谢
It seems like we have to keep waiting.
看来继续等下去
It will be us who suffer
遭殃的会是我们
(Rong Guang Offal Soup)
(荣光内脏汤)
Brother, why have you never brought me here?
大哥为什么从来没带我来过这里
Your eyes are going to shoot out lasers
你眼里要射出雷射光了
I'm here to protect my brother
我是为了保护大哥
I just sent a few people to follow him
才派了几个人跟着他
Wasn't it to kill him?
不是为了干掉他吗
I'm definitely considering it
我确实有在考虑
Bastard
混蛋
He actually accepted someone like you into a gang Brother is so pitiful
竟然收你这种人入帮派 大哥真可怜
you bastard
你这混蛋
Are you just as pitiful?
你也一样可怜吧
So funny
笑死人了
You will one day...
你总有一天…
Will die in my hands
会死在我手里
Hello Yongbi
喂 永弼
Don’t just be responsible for driving away the demolition households
别只是负责赶走拆迁户
How about participating directly in the program?
直接参与计划怎么样
What? Directly involved?
什么 直接参与吗
We hold 70% of the shares and you hold 30%
股分我们占七成 您占三成
We will give you 10% more shares
我们会多给您一成的股分
because of money laundering and tax expenses
是因为洗钱和税金方面的支出
All included in Boss Lian’s shares
都包含在廉老板的股分里
Benefits brought by comprehensive urban renewal in the metropolitan area I heard it’s an astronomical figure
首都圈全面都更所带来的利益 听说是天文数字
Brother, didn't he tell you this?
大哥没跟你说这些吧
And…
还有…
I heard you plan to travel from Incheon Import large quantities of drugs
听说你打算从仁川 进口大量的毒品
That was paid for by my eldest brother, right?
那是大哥出钱的吧
obvious
显而易见
He is raising funds to develop the company I want you to sell drugs
他是为了筹措开发公司的资金 才要你卖毒品
Then secretly leak the information to the police get rid of you
之后再偷偷泄露情报给警察 除掉你
From the elder brother's point of view
在大哥的立场
He eats both sides
他是两边通吃
How about you? You are pitiful too, right?
怎么样 你也很可怜吧
So what do you want, brat?
所以你想怎么样 臭小子
You have been with him your whole life
你跟了他一辈子
He wants to get rid of you
他都想除掉你了
People like me who are halfway to becoming a monk What will happen
像我这种半路出家的人 会有什么下场
He must...
他一定…
will drive me away
会赶走我
Go back to you
找你回去
Isn't it?
不是吗
Yongbi
永弼
Let's pull down the eldest brother together
我们一起把大哥拉下来
Then grab Du Geng's career.
然后把都更事业抢过来吧
I'll go back right away
我马上就回去
what's going on
这是怎么回事
what happened
发生了什么事
Brother Douxue successfully rebelled
斗学哥成功造反
He finally became a nationally renowned gangster.
终于成为全国知名的黑道老大了
This is a place to witness history
这里是见证历史的现场
Douxue?
斗学呢
Where is Douxue?
斗学在哪
he is injured
他受伤了
are you okay
您没事吧
I'm going to be scolded again
我又要被骂啦
What is this?
这算什么嘛
Okay, it's okay
好了 没关系
Don't do this
别这样
blood will get on you
血会沾到你身上
I'm fine
我没事
Being a gangster means you will get hurt occasionally.
混黑道本来就偶尔会受伤
You hateful gangster
你这可恶的流氓
let's break up
我们分手吧
You're hurt like this and bleeding
你这样受伤 流血
Beat someone
打人
I can't seem to help it...
我好像没办法…
See you like this again
再看你这样了
I won't forget...
我不会忘记…
The heart you gave me
你曾付出给我的心意
Don't get hurt
你别受伤
Take good care of yourself
好好保重身体
"Can I come back to you again?"
"我能再回到你身边吗"
"trembling eyes"
"颤抖的眼神"
"Looks more sad"
"显得更加哀戚"
"My heart is swaying in the desolate sky" Looking at you, the days we spent in love
"我的心在荒凉的天空中飘摇" 看着你 我们相爱过的日子
"your name"
"你的名字"
"It's deeply etched in my heart"
"深深刻在我心上"
Hey, what's wrong with you?
喂 你怎么了吗
"Where did it all go wrong?"
"从哪里开始出错的"
Hey Wu Dingchen, what's wrong with you?
喂 吴定辰 你怎么了
I still said it
我还是说出来了
what
什么
I broke up with him...
我跟他提分手了…
I told Douxue not to meet each other again.
我跟斗学说别再见面了
what
什么
"It's all in the past"
"都是过去的事了"
"Cannot hide"
"无法隐藏"
"Missing you"
"对你的思念"
"It broke out"
"就此爆发"
"Can I come back to you again?"
"我能再回到你身边吗"
"trembling eyes"
"颤抖的眼神"
"Looks more sad"
"显得更加哀戚"
Brother, I'm here to get you some clothes.
大哥 帮你拿衣服来了
are you okay
你没事吧
I don't know what to do either
我也不知道该怎么办了
Okay, don't make any noise
好了 不要吵
Hello Liu Yongbi
喂 柳永弼
You really got into big trouble this time
你这次真的闯大祸了
I see you are in black and white now in prison or outside
我看你现在在黑白两道 在狱里或在外面
You all have to ask for happiness.
都要自求多福了
You're still smiling
你还笑啊
Call the prosecutor in charge.
叫负责的检察官来
Not a lawyer?
不是律师吗
To Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong
对 崔哲雄检察官
call him
叫他来
Don't worry you'll see him soon
不用担心 你很快就会见到他了
You can't treat me like this
你们不可以这样对待我
Call him right away
马上叫他来
are you crazy Who allowed you to yell and scream here?
你是不是疯啦 谁准你在这里大呼小叫
what are you doing
你在干嘛
what is that
那是什么
Prosecutor's Office
大检察厅
Holder of this document Assisted prosecutors in their investigation
持有此文件者 协助了检方的调查
Death free gold medal
免死金牌
General Yi Sun-shin received
李舜臣将军收到过的
what are you talking about
你在说什么
This time I...
我这次…
I did that to help the prosecutor catch Lian Guangzhuo.
是为了帮检方抓廉光卓才会那样
This is the death certificate the prosecutor gave me
这是检察官给我的免死证明
Look underneath yourself
你自己看底下
There is the fingerprint of Prosecutor Choi Cheol-woong underneath.
底下有崔哲雄检察官的手印
and the seal of the Director of the Prosecutor's Office
和检察厅厅长的印章
That's right
没错
It has the official seal of the Director of the Prosecutor's Office
是有检察厅厅长的公章
But I only know the Attorney General
但我只认识检察总长
Who is the prosecutor general?
检察厅长是谁啊
Ignorant guy
无知的家伙
You don’t even know the boss in the prosecutor’s office?
你连检察院里的老大都不认识啊
Don’t know…
不认识…
Hey look at your friend
喂 看看你朋友
look at him
看看他
Don’t know…
不认识…
Really
真是的
I'm telling you, you messed with the wrong person.
我告诉你 你惹错人了
do you know who i am
你知道我是谁吗
I don’t know, brat
不知道 臭小子
These are items confiscated from Lian Guangzhuo's home
这些是从廉光卓家没收来的物品
(Wu Wanxu)
(吴万旭)
Why is this here?
这怎么会在这
Brother, you are here
大哥 你来啦
is he in there
他在里面吗
He's in there, bro
他在里面 大哥
Are you here for this matter?
你是为了这次的事来的吗
Otherwise, what will happen if I come?
不然我来还会有什么事
you should know that person Related to our company
你应该知道那个人 和我们公司有关联
I don't know
我不知道
If only I knew
要是知道
The minister won't agree either
部长也不会答应
To be honest, we need Lian Guangzhuo very much
老实说 我们很需要廉光卓
End the case quickly and don’t let the media hype it up
快终结案件 别让媒体炒作
Let’s just say that the whole incident was caused by Yoo Young-pil’s desire for revenge.
就说整起事件是柳永弼想报仇
As requested by the master
照老爷的请求
I have already agreed to let Li Dou learn from it. Take the responsibility for the demolition violence
已经说好让李斗学 扛下拆迁暴力的责任了
what
什么
what does that mean
那是什么意思
I didn’t expect that Master…
没想到老爷…
But suddenly he was involved in the underworld struggle
却突然被卷入黑道斗争
I didn't know there was such a thing
我不知道有这种事
What is your relationship with Li Douxue?
你跟李斗学是什么关系
What is the relationship?
到底是什么关系
He will ask you to ask someone to follow him
会让你拜托人去跟着他
Also helped him rise to power Make him a gang boss
还帮助他上位 让他成为黑帮老大
Are you...
你是不是…
Do you owe him anything?
欠了他什么吗
There is no such thing
没有那种事
I've said it before
我以前说过吧
Master can have today
老爷能有今天
All credit must go to Mr.
都要功归于先生
But now he...
但他现在…
may be disappointed
可能很失望
I heard that you don’t like eating sour food
听说您不喜欢吃酸的
I only picked the sweet ones
我只挑了甜的来
Please eat, brother
请吃吧 大哥
That guy Yongpil
永弼那家伙
Not so bold
没那么大胆
It's impossible to plan such a thing alone
不可能单独计划这种事
There must be someone behind it You must find that person, Douxue
一定有背后主使 你一定要找出那个人 斗学
Brother, is the apple taste okay?
大哥 苹果的味道还可以吗
Is Apple important now?
现在苹果重要吗
You must find out the mastermind behind it
你一定要去找出背后主使
The police are already investigating
警方已经在调查了
The truth will soon come to light
很快就会水落石出的
Hey brat
喂 臭小子
When did we start trusting the police?
我们什么时候开始信警察了
Go find it, you brat
你去找出来 臭小子
what are you doing
你在做什么
What a pity it would be to throw this away
这丢掉多可惜啊
Come, take them all and eat them
来 你全部拿去吃吧
Big brother
大哥
Actually I have found...
其实我已经找到…
The mastermind behind this
背后主使了
Really?
是吗
Who is he? What kind of guy is he?
是谁 是什么样的家伙
it's me
是我
Brother, I actually set the trap
大哥 其实是我设的局
You…
你…
you bastard
你这混蛋
You'd better just call it a day
您还是就此收山吧
Don't let my hard-working brother Contemporary sinners go to jail
别让辛苦的弟弟 当代罪羔羊去坐牢
Li Douxue
李斗学
Let him take the responsibility for violent demolition
让他扛下暴力拆迁的责任
Send him to jail
送他去坐牢吧
I will do as you ask
我会照您的吩咐做
Anyway, I plan to find an opportunity to deal with him.
反正我也打算找机会处理掉他
Got it
知道了
You go out
你出去吧
I want to be alone for a while
我想一个人静一静
Brother, are you here to visit the doctor?
大哥 您是来探病的吗
how is he
他怎么样了
You don't have to go in
您可以不用进去了
what does it mean
什么意思
Although the operation was successful
虽然手术很成功
But he decided to close the mountain
但他决定收山了
He can't help it...
他没办法…
I'll be your hunting dog again.
再当你们的猎犬了
Really?
是吗
What a pity
真可惜
No
不
You have a smarter hound
你们多了条更聪明的猎犬
In fact, this is all my plan
其实这一切都是我的计划
Please arrange it
请您安排一下吧
I want to show my loyalty to my master
我想对主人表示我的忠诚
First meeting Hello
初次见面 您好
My name is Li Douxue
我叫李斗学
Do you want to die?
你是不是想死啊
I want to live
我想活下去
Then you still dare to hinder my business?
那你还敢妨碍我做生意
I don't understand your business
我不了解您的生意
Just act first to survive
只是为了生存抢先行动而已
You don't understand my business
你不了解我的生意
All I know is that you want us to drive away the bad guys.
我只知道您要我们赶走钉子户
I don't know anything else
除此之外 我什么都不知道
you are not a hound
你不是猎犬
If it was a hunting dog, the owner would tell him to die. he will die
是猎犬的话 主人叫他去死 他就会去死
you are a mad dog
你就是只疯狗
Will bite his master back
会反咬主人的
Brother Guangzhuo
光卓哥
Not my master, we are brothers
不是我的主人 我们是兄弟
I...will never bite my master
我…绝对不咬主人
If you are willing to be my master
如果您愿意当我的主人
When the time comes, if you want me to die, I will die too
到时候 您要我去死我也会去死
Really?
是吗
OK I promise you
好 我答应你
Go to hell
去死吧
This is the hound you killed me the price that must be paid
这是你杀了我的猎犬 所必须付出的代价
Isn’t this what you said yourself just now?
这不是你刚才自己说的吗
It's very simple to say, right?
用说的很简单吧
How about it? Can't do it?
怎么样 做不到吗
Then stop looking for death and continue being a mad dog.
那就别找死了 继续当条疯狗吧
You kid is really a mad dog
你这小子真的是条疯狗
drink
喝吧
How do you know there are no bullets in the gun?
你怎么知道枪里没有子弹
If you really want to kill me You can just find someone to do something to me.
您如果真的要杀我 大可找人对我动手就好
No need to do it yourself
不需要亲自出马
For a gangster, you have a very quick mind.
以流氓而言 你脑筋动满快的嘛
What is your relationship with Cui Cheol-woong?
你跟崔哲雄是什么关系
We have been brothers since childhood...
我们从小就称兄道弟…
Does Cui Cheol-woong owe you anything?
崔哲雄有欠你什么吗
Even if you have known each other as brothers since childhood
即便你们从小就以兄弟相称
The prosecutor shouldn't have stepped in to help either. Gangsters seize power in gangs, right?
检察官也不该插手帮忙 流氓在帮派里夺权上位吧
between you two What happened
你们两个之间 到底发生过什么事
Is it possible that you have been in jail on his behalf?
难不成你代替他坐过牢吗
You recruit from the real situation
你从实招来
I saved his life
我救了他一命
When Choi Cheol-woong was a mole in the student movement group I helped him a lot
崔哲雄在学运团体里当内鬼时 我帮了他不少忙
Is that really all there is to it?
真的只有这样吗
Yes
对
I want him to repay the favor he owed me at that time
我要他偿还当时欠我的人情
really sorry
真的很抱歉
Li Douxue
李斗学
yes
是的
You are my hound from today on
你从今天起就是我的猎犬
And you've never seen the master's face
而且你从没看过主人的脸
We haven't met today either
我们今天也没见过面
If I want you to bite, you have to bite. If I want you to die, you have to die.
我要你咬人就得咬人 要你死你就得死
I will keep it in mind
我会谨记在心
Team leader Wu will explain to you what happens next.
之后的事 吴组长会再交代你
Big brother
大哥
Your wound won't open again, will it?
你的伤口不会又裂开了吧
I really almost died
我真的差点挂掉
Really…
真是的…
Not only is he smart, he is also calm and capable.
他不但很聪明 还很沉着大器
He knows exactly what we're going to do
他很清楚我们要做什么
and got rid of their boss
并除掉了他们的老大
That's why he said he wanted to see me
所以他才会说要见我吧
If you are worried
如果您不放心
I'll get rid of him
我会把他处理掉
No time to find someone again
没时间重新找人了
Let's observe him for a while first
先观察他一阵子吧
I know
我知道了
Big brother
大哥
You should go to the hospital first
你应该先去医院吧
The wound needs to be re-sutured, right?
伤口要重新缝合才行吧
Did you fight again?
你又去打架了吗
Do you want me to see you like this? Did you just ask me to come?
你是想让我看到你这副模样 才叫我来的吗
I've seen it, okay?
我已经看到了 可以了吧
I'm leaving
我要走了
Dingchen
定辰
If I don't join the underworld...
我如果不混黑道…
Do you want to live with me?
你愿意跟我过日子吗
I asked you to come because I planned to leave the underworld.
我是打算离开黑道才叫你来的
I thought about it carefully
我仔细想过了
in my hardest time
在我最辛苦的时候
It was you who grabbed my hand
是你抓住了我的手
When I went to agricultural high school
我去念农业高中时
When I went to jail there was...
我去坐牢时 还有…
The last time you came to my house to see me
上次你来我家找我时
Every time something bad happens... I feel like this is my fate
每次遇到那些烂事… 我都觉得是我命该如此
That's why I left you on purpose
所以才故意离开你
But
但是
I don't want to do that anymore
我不想再那样做了
Dingchen, please don’t give up on me
定辰 拜托你别放弃我
I will leave the underworld
我会离开黑道
Have a proper job and live a life
做个正当的工作过生活
I can't live without you
没有你我活不下去
I love you Dingchen
我爱你 定辰
Have you ever considered my mood
你有没有考虑过我的心情
I've already made up my mind to leave you
我都已经下定决心要离开你了
you idiot
你这个笨蛋
"I wanna hold your hand"
"I wanna holding your hand"
"I wanna be like a birthday" What to do…
"I wanna be like a birthday" 怎么办…
"No matter you will be here"
"No matter you will be here"
"Forever love the only one"
"Forever love the only one"
"I wanna look at your mind"
"I wanna look at your mind"
"Take me your eyes"
"Take me your eyes"
"Let me in beautiful your life"
"Let me in beautiful your life"
"Come over here"
"Come over here"
"Back in your love in my life"
"Back in your love in my life"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in your life"
"Let me go in your life"
"Love you no more"
"Love you no more"
"I wanna be myself"
"I wanna be myself"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in my life"
"I wanna hold your hand"
"I wanna holding your hand"
"I wanna be like a birthday"
"I wanna be like a birthday"
Yes brother
是的 大哥
You guys are leaving
你们走啦
Get out of the way...
闪开…
You didn't ask us to come, you drove us away.
你不是叫我们来 是赶我们走喔
Big brother wants us to leave
大哥要我们走啦
Won't it be cold?
不会冷吗
very warm
很温暖
"Come over here"
"Come over here"
"Back in your love in my life"
"Back in your love in my life"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in your life" (Seoul Hospital)
"Let me go in your life" (首尔医院)
"Love you no more"
"Love you no more"
"I wanna be myself"
"I wanna be myself"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in your life"
"Let me go in your life"
"Love you no more"
"Love you no more"
"I wanna be myself"
"I wanna be myself"
"Let me go in my life"
"Let me go in my life"
There are Mundong and Sinhwadong
那里是文洞和新华洞
The whole area is a slum. It will flood whenever it rains
整片都是贫民窟 只要下雨就会淹水
A total of 14,000 square meters of land All included in the update plan
共一万四千坪的土地 都纳入都更计划
Mingtangdong is completely incomparable to this place.
名堂洞完全不能跟这里比呢
The original intention was to build houses for the common people.
原本的用意是想替平民盖住宅
But it doesn't make much money
但这赚不到什么钱
Coupled with the rush to raise funds for the Olympic Games
再加上急着筹措奥运会的资金
It was changed to building high-end apartments.
就改成兴建高级公寓了
There will probably be serious protests from the residents.
居民应该会严重抗议吧
It's useless even if they protest
就算他们抗议也没用
It doesn't matter what the superior has to sacrifice.
上级无论要牺牲什么都无所谓
This plan is imperative
这个计划势在必行
Our commander's mobility is amazing.
我们的长官行动力很惊人啊
Is there a lot of land available to buy over there?
那边还有很多土地可以买吗
There are many more
还有很多
How much is the profit after development?
开发后的利润大概有多少呢
Just what the government can earn At least one trillion won
光是政府能赚到的 少说也有一兆韩元
Land will make money
土地会生财啊
But I need to update the place It's not just here
不过要都更的地方 也不是只有这里
are you okay
你没事吧
OMG... they are so sweet.
天啊… 他们还真甜蜜
According to the map, just after we came out This is Mundong
按照地图 我们刚刚出来之后 这边就是文洞
Next to it is Xinhuadong
旁边就是新华洞
There are a lot of slums here
这边有很多贫民窟
Over here
这边呢
Ouch
哎唷
Why are you eating instant noodles again?
你怎么又吃泡面
There should be rice in the rice pot, right?
饭锅里应该有饭吧
Why are you coming home later and later?
你怎么越来越晚回家了
Really, am I an office worker?
真是的 难道我是上班族吗
Is there any fixed time to get off work?
哪有固定的下班时间
I don’t want to think about who asked me to help her...
不想想是谁叫我帮她做事的…
Where is Tetsuo?
哲雄呢
Did he come home to see him?
他有回家看看吗
He is too busy at work
他的工作太忙
Rented a room near his office
在他办公室附近租了一间房住
Having said that, I think Tetsuo's mother It seems like she will remarry
话说回来 我觉得哲雄的妈妈 好像会改嫁耶
Don't talk nonsense
你不要乱讲话
Maybe that person is just a relative
那个人说不定只是亲戚
Stop lying
少骗人了
She said that person was her cousin
她说那个人是她的表哥
How can any cousins hold hands lovingly?
哪有表兄妹会恩爱地牵着小手啊
Madam is the daughter-in-law of a famous family Besides, Tetsuo is still here
夫人可是名门望族的媳妇 况且还有哲雄在
She won't remarry easily
她才不会轻易改嫁
It's so depressing
真让人郁闷耶
Scarecrow in the field They are more observant than you
连田里的稻草人 都比你还会察言观色
Help her prepare a place to stay
帮她准备住处
What kind of salon should I open for her?
帮她开什么沙龙店
Now I'm still looking at the land with her.
现在还陪她看土地耶
Not siblings
又不是亲兄妹
How could it be possible to be so nice to her and hurt like this?
怎么可能对她那么好 疼成这样
And that man is so handsome
而且那个人长得那么英俊
Stop talking and clear the table.
别再说了 把餐桌收一收啦
I'm a woman who goes out to work and make money.
我可是出去工作赚钱的女人
You collect it yourself
你自己收
Dou Xue’s mother…
斗学的妈…
Did that woman take the wrong medicine?
那个女人是吃错药了吗
Be careful...
小心点…
Where did you go and drink so much?
你去哪里喝了那么多酒
what
什么
Do you really want to quit the gang?
你真的要退出帮派吗
Yes
对
I don't want to be a third-rate gangster anymore.
我现在不想再当三流的小混混了
If Kwang Tak or Yong Pil comes to seek revenge on you again
要是光卓或永弼又去找你报仇
What will you do then
到时你要怎么办
They would never dare to do such a thing
他们绝对不敢做这种事
Don't worry
你就别担心了
Why didn't you discuss it with us?
你怎么都不跟我们商量
Is it too much?
会不会太过分了
Since we joined together
既然我们是一起加入的
We should go to the end together
就该一起走到最后吧
Can a person who is the boss leave at will?
当老大的人难道可以说走就走吗
That's right
没错
Boss, you really let us down.
老大 你真让我们失望
Should I discuss it with you?
难道跟你们商量
Will you let me go?
你们就会放我走吗
Boy, what are we going to do?
小子 那我们要怎么办
Are you going to part ways with us?
你是要跟我们分道扬镳吗
Really?
是吗
I...I knew it would be like this
我…我就知道会这样
Unfaithful guy
没义气的家伙
Now you get huge benefits for yourself
你现在自己拿到天大的好处
Just don’t want to divide us
就不想分我们吧
So you guys...
所以你们这群小子…
Let these gentlemen disband.
这几位先生就解散吧
Brother, let’s go too
大哥 我们也走吧
this traitor
这个叛徒
Let's go, brother, get out...
走吧 大哥 出去吧…
Let's go Everyone, please wait a moment
快走吧 各位 请等一下
In order to carry out legal contracting works
为了进行合法的承包工程
So he has to leave the illegal gang
所以他必须离开非法的帮派
Am I right?
我说得没错吧
If you are undertaking a contracting project I should really need your help, Brother Feng Hao.
进行承包工程的话 应该很需要风浩哥你们的帮忙
Stop committing illegal real estate fraud today
如今别再做非法的房地产诈欺了
Let’s invest in real estate development legally
我们来合法投入房地产开发吧
I knew that was the case
我就知道是这么回事
family Yes, we are a family
一家人 没错 我们是一家人
He is indeed our boss
真不愧是我们的老大
you are the best
你最棒了
Brother, you have to be by my side too
哥 你也要在我身边才行
Of course
那当然
As for Jisoo hyung and Sunwoo...
至于吉洙哥跟宣宇…
Choose yourselves
你们自己选吧
To join our contracting project
要加入我们的承包工程
Still have to leave the gang
还是要离开帮派
No matter which path you choose
无论你们选哪一条路
I'll give you all the contractor shares
我都会给你们承包商的股分
Really…
真是的…
I don’t want to fight or kill
我也不想打打杀杀
Want to wear a suit and tie all day
想要整天穿西装 打领带
It must be super cool to commute to work like this
这样上下班一定超帅的
But I haven’t read the book
但我又没读过书
Jisoo hyung, isn’t it?
吉洙哥 不是吗
Xuanyu
宣宇
Large companies also have security departments
大公司里也有保全警卫部门
You don't have to worry about finding a job
你不用担心找不到工作
The most important thing is
最重要的是
You need to eliminate the gangster nature in your body
你们要消除体内流氓的本性
Do you know
知道吗
Is it the nature of a gangster?
流氓的本性吗
How to eliminate this
这要怎么消除
Could it be that when I was still in my mother’s arms? Is he just a gangster?
难道我还在妈妈怀里时 就是流氓了吗
Really?
是吗
If my family situation is okay
要是我家境没问题的话
Neither will I...
我也不会…
Okay, then let's do the contracting project together.
好 那我们就一起做承包工程吧
good
好
I don't want
我不要
what
什么
If everyone went into contracting projects
如果大家都去做承包工程
Who will be responsible for the demolition work?
谁来负责拆迁作业
And is it a contracting project? Can you avoid dirty things at all?
而且难道做承包工程 就可以完全不碰肮脏事了吗
Demolition is simply demolishing a house
拆迁就是单纯拆房子而已
Just leave it to others to do
交给其他人做就好
Xuanyu and I can't give up The nature of being a gangster
我跟宣宇无法舍弃 身为流氓的本性
We should stay in the gang
我们要留在帮派才对
Wait...
等等…
Come on, you brat
快走啦 臭小子
Goodbye
再见啦
It seems I can give up my gangster nature.
我好像可以舍弃流氓的本性耶
Then see you later, Luo
那就之后见罗
OK
好的
Xuanyu…
宣宇…
That kid really loves to be cool
那小子真爱耍帅
Really
真是的
Brother, we really can’t give up Is it the nature of a gangster?
大哥 我们真的无法舍弃 流氓的本性吗
Xuanyu
宣宇
Usually when cleaning the house
通常家里大扫除时
Not only do we have to clean the kitchen
不但要把厨房擦干净
The floor also needs to be mopped, right?
地板也要擦干净 对吧
Yes
是啊
So what should I use to wipe it?
那要用什么来擦呢
Wipe the kitchen with a clean rag
厨房用干净的抹布擦
The floor is wiped with a dirty rag
地板用肮脏的抹布擦
Right
对啊
Doo Hak and Hyung Soo will be the clean rags
斗学跟亨洙就去当干净的抹布
The two of us are going to be dirty rags
我们两个要当肮脏的抹布
Do you say we are dirty rags?
你说我们是肮脏的抹布吗
Brat, there's nothing wrong with that.
臭小子 这没什么不好的
I don't want to be a dirty rag
我不想当肮脏的抹布耶
It's just that the roles are different
只是角色不同而已
Anyway, both kinds of rags can clean the house Polish it until it shines
反正两种抹布都能把家里 擦得闪闪发亮啊
But why don’t you ask me first every time? Just without permission...
但你怎么每次都不先问我 就擅自…
Because I don't want to be separated from you
因为我不想跟你分开啊
Let's just do what we're good at
我们就做自己擅长的事吧
We're going to be the boss now, brat.
我们现在要当老板了 臭小子
Are you in charge of a hotel or a nightclub?
你要负责饭店还是夜总会
Brother, you choose first
大哥 你先选吧
You kid...
你这小子…
Brother, you choose first.
弟弟你先选吧
Really?
真的吗
Really
真的
Then I want to choose a hotel
那我要选饭店
I want to choose a hotel...
我想选饭店耶…
Then why are you asking me?
那你干嘛还问我
Hello…
喂…
Can't you put me in charge of the hotel?
不能让我负责饭店吗
Come here
你过来一下
Does Tetsuo like Douxue's girlfriend?
哲雄喜欢斗学的女朋友吗
why didn't you tell me
你怎么没告诉我
I was going to report to you
我正打算向您报告
But…
不过…
Between Lee Doo Hak and Prosecutor Choi It’s not just a women’s problem
李斗学跟崔检察官之间 不只有女人的问题
The deputy chief is also related to the two of them.
次长也跟他们两个有所关联
You seem too hasty
你好像太急了
Is it for Dingchen?
是为了定辰吗
I can't get married as a gangster.
我总不能以流氓的身分结婚嘛
you are right
你想得很对
When are you planning to get married?
你们打算什么时候结婚
Well... let's wait until the contracting project is on track.
嗯…等承包工程上轨道之后吧
(Manager Li Douxue)
(李斗学经理)
That's no wonder you're so anxious
那也难怪你那么急了
But you should know
不过你应该知道
The more times this happens, the more cautious you should be.
越是这种时候 越要谨慎行事吧
Li Dou learns to be a contractor?
李斗学做承包商吗
He's just a little hooligan Are you sure you can hand over the contracting work to him?
他不过是个小流氓 你们确定能把承包作业交给他吗
After several twists and turns, some accidents happened
几经波折之后发生了一些意外
The deputy commander had no choice
次长他也别无选择
I will introduce Tetsuo to the deputy minister soon
我很快就会将哲雄介绍给次长
Then we will soon...
那我们很快…
We will become a family, right?
就会成为一家人了吧
between family members
家人之间
No secrets
不可以有秘密
Got it
知道了吧
before becoming a family
在成为一家人之前
There's one more thing you need to know
还有一件事必须让您知道
Please come in
请进
I came too late, right?
是我太晚来了吧
Tetsuo
哲雄
This is the gentleman I told you about
这位就是我跟你提过的先生
Prosecutor Choi, nice to meet you.
崔检察官 很开心能见到你
Young people who contribute to the country
为国家贡献的年轻人
Don't be discouraged
千万不能泄气
See you next time
我们下次见
After ending our military school life, we separated.
结束军校生活后 我们就分开了
It took a long time before we met again
经过了好长一段岁月才再度重逢
Am I doing an interview?
我这是在面试吗
because of my mother Will you always take care of me secretly?
因为我母亲的关系 你才会一直在暗地里关照我吗
After I was captured and sent to the army
我被抓去军队之后
met someone A guy who is no different from a devil
遇见了一个 跟恶魔没两样的家伙
He said someone would help me become a prosecutor
他说有人会帮助我当上检察官
It turns out that person is the deputy chief
原来那个人就是次长
You and mediator Wu Wanxu...
您跟吴万旭调停官…
Have we worked together for a long time?
共事很久了吧
I worked with him when I was a squadron captain. This should be considered a long time
我当中队长时就跟他一起共事 这样应该算满久了
So…
那么…
When he was at the Security Command
他在保安司令部时
You also work together
你们也一起共事罗
It's almost time for him to arrive
他差不多该到了
Prosecutor Choi
崔检察官
every time i see you Everybody feels very heavy
我每次见到你 都觉得心情很沉重
I know it's too late to say this now
我知道现在说这些为时已晚
but i'm really sorry Those things I did to you
但我真的非常抱歉 曾经对你做过那些事
Forcing Prosecutor Choi to enlist in the army
逼崔检察官强制入伍
And forcing you to be a mole? It has nothing to do with the deputy chief
还有逼你做内鬼的事 都跟次长无关
I also did it after you passed the judicial examination
我也是在你司法考试合格后
I just found out that you are my wife’s son
才知道你是夫人的儿子
The things I did to you were not my intentions
对你做的那些事 并非我的本意
please forgive me
请你原谅我
The deputy minister was completely unaware of those things.
次长对那些事完全不知情
Everything was instigated by me
一切都是我唆使的
sorry please forgive me
对不起 请原谅我
I will spend my whole life atonement and compensation to you two
我会用一辈子向两位赎罪和补偿
And loyal to both of them
并且效忠两位
stand up
站起来
I'll just wait and see
我就等着看
How will you atone and pledge your allegiance?
你会怎么赎罪和效忠
I really wanted to die at that time
我当时真的很想死
I even wrote a suicide note
我甚至还写好了遗书
But I believe I can take revenge one day
但我相信总有一天能够报仇
I relied on this belief to survive.
靠着这个信念撑了下来
Tetsuo thank you
哲雄 谢谢你
thank you for surviving
谢谢你活下来
Mom couldn't survive without you
如果没有你 妈也活不下来
Prosecutor Choi, I’m sorry.
崔检察官 对不起
Although I also feel very sad
虽然我也觉得很心痛
But when doing things for the country
但为国家做事时
Occasionally, some people will be sacrificed by accident.
偶尔会阴错阳差牺牲掉某些人
I apologize to you on behalf of the country
我代替国家向你道歉
really sorry
真的很抱歉
A sacrifice made by accident?
阴错阳差的牺牲吗
Mom, I can't accept your marriage.
妈 我没办法接受你们的婚事
Tetsuo
哲雄
These people are not human at all
这些人根本不是人
They are not human beings…
他们不是人…
It's a bunch of monsters
是一群怪物
Do you want to choose the monster or me?
要选择怪物 还是选择我
you decide
你自己决定
So cold
好冷喔
(Terrible outsider team) what
(可怕的外人球团) 什么
Do you want us to change the title?
你要我们改片名吗
Yes, please change the title of the film
对 请改片名
"Terrible outsider team" What's wrong with this title?
"可怕的外人球团" 这个片名到底有什么问题
Most people have read the original comic
大部分的民众都看过原作漫画啦
Our Performance Ethics Committee believes that The word "terrible"
我们公演伦理委员会认为 "可怕"这个单字
May contribute to an atmosphere of social panic
可能会助长社会恐慌的氛围
Please remove the word "terrible"
请把"可怕"两个字拿掉
Section Chief, as you say
科长 照你这样说
"The daughter rescued from the mire" is also possible Throwing society into a quagmire
"泥沼中救出的女儿"也可能 害社会陷入一片泥沼
"Killing battlefield" will bring social Turned into a killing scene
"杀戮战场"会把社会 变成杀戮现场罗
When these movies were released The Performance Ethics Committee has not been established yet.
这些电影发行时 公演伦理委员会还没成立啊
Instead of doing this, you might as well be like before Big Thorns conducts movie content censorship
与其这样 你们还不如像以前 大刺刺进行电影内容审查
what review we are review
什么审查 我们是审议
It is up to us to judge the standards of social ethics
社会伦理的标准 由我们来判断
If you don’t change the title of the film
如果你们不改片名
Don't even think about showing it
就别想要上映
Wait...
等等…
(Principal Wu Dingchen)
(吴定辰负责人)
They are really humorous
他们还真是幽默耶
If you remove the word "terrible" There are only four words left: "outsider team"
如果把"可怕"两个字拿掉 只剩"外人球团"四个字
It would be super weird
会超级奇怪耶
(Principal Wu Dingchen) That is to say
(吴定辰负责人) 就是说啊
You have to find other words to replace it.
要找其他单字代替才行
"Terrible outsider team"
"骇人的外人球团"
"The unrivaled outsider team"
"天下无敌的外人球团"
Or "a brave and capable outsider team"
还是"骁勇善战的外人球团"
This isn't some Navy baseball team.
这又不是什么海军棒球团
Since it is a work directed by Lee Chang-ho
既然是李长浩导演的作品
How about just replacing it with the director’s name?
直接用导演名字取代怎么样
Very good
很好
"Lee Jang-ho's outsider team"?
"李长浩的外人球团"吗
Yes
对
Let’s ask Director Li for his opinion.
问问看李导演的意见吧
OK
好的
But I feel like the movie business is so boring lately
但我最近觉得做电影生意好无聊
Because of the amendment to the film law
因为电影法修法
Now anyone can make and import movies
现在谁都可以制作和进口电影
plus the popularity of television and videotapes
加上电视和录影带普及
The glory days of cinema are over
电影的辉煌时代已经结束了
And the production costs are still rising.
而且制作费还不断上涨
But as long as we make great movies
但只要我们做出优秀的电影
Those second-rate film companies It will close itself
那些二流的电影公司 就会自己关门的
than excellent works I should make something that can sell well.
比起优秀的作品 应该制作能大卖的作品吧
Don't forget that your mother is a businesswoman
别忘了你妈可是个生意人
You are here
你来啦
(Nandao Film Company)
(南道电影公司)
who is he
他是谁
he is my boyfriend
他是我男朋友
You have a boyfriend
你交男朋友罗
OMG…
天啊…
He's tall and handsome.
身材很高䠷 满帅的嘛
what's your name
你叫什么名字
My name is Li Douxue
我叫李斗学
nice to meet you
很高兴认识你
What happened to you? You got a boyfriend...
你是怎么回事 交了男朋友…
I didn’t even tell my mother that I had a boyfriend.
交了男朋友都不跟妈妈说
Don’t you know it now?
你现在不就知道了吗
I am Dingchen’s mother. I am her mother.
我是定辰的妈妈 我是她妈
My name is Che Jinyu
我叫车锦玉
so happy to meet you
真开心能见到你
Yes, I'm happy to meet you too.
是的 我也很开心能见到您
You came just in time
你来得正好
let's eat together
我们一起吃饭吧
I know a good restaurant
我知道一间不错的餐厅
Mom, we have an appointment
妈 我们跟人有约了
Ouch, who did you make an appointment with?
哎唷 你们跟谁约好了
Are you going to eat with anyone else?
你们要跟其他人吃饭吗
Is there anyone more important than me as a mother?
有人比我这个妈妈还重要吗
It’s so sad…
真让人伤心…
Who is it?
是谁啊
It's my mother in the nursing home.
是在疗养院的妈妈
Then go to the appointment
那你去赴约吧
Gao Standing Committee Yes
高常务 是
Let's have a bowl of cold noodles and then go back.
我们吃碗冷面再回去吧
OK
好的
Then let’s see Luo next time
那我们下次见罗
Please walk slowly
请慢走
nice to meet you
很高兴认识你
She is your mother
她是你妈喔
Husband
老公
"You fool"
"你这个傻瓜"
"If you can't catch him, express your feelings."
"要是无法抓住他 将心意表明"
Aunt…
伯母…
"You're just a fool"
"你就是个傻瓜"
mouth open
嘴巴张开
OK
好的
"If you can't catch him, tell him you love you" Is it delicious?
"要是无法抓住他 对他说爱你" 好吃吗
Dingchen, you can eat too
定辰 你也吃吧
"He is leaving you"
"他就要离你而去了"
Does it taste okay?
味道还可以吗
Super delicious
超好吃
"Speak quickly" My hands are black
"快点开口吧" 我的手黑掉了
I'll wipe it for you
我帮你擦
I should be allowed to bake it
应该让我来烤才对
"On the unmarked streets and alleys"
"在不着痕迹的大街小巷上"
"Only those who cannot speak"
"只有开不了口的人"
Thank you for your hard work today
今天辛苦你了
I'm really sorry
我真的很抱歉
I went to see my aunt too late
是我太晚去见伯母了
Don't say that. Thank you for accompanying me to see her.
别这么说 谢谢你陪我去看她
Go back quickly and have a good rest
快回去 好好休息吧
good
好
Dingchen
定辰
Since these days
这段日子以来
You all live a life where you are forced to grow up
你都过着被迫长大的生活
It must be very hard
一定很辛苦
"The moment my eyes met yours" But I...
"和你四目相接的那瞬间" 但我…
But so ignorant
却那么不懂事
"It's like the air is condensed" sorry
"仿佛连空气也凝结般" 对不起
"I move slowly, don't want to miss it"
"我慢慢地移动 不想错过"
"My eyes are full of you" from now on
"双眸里满是你的身影" 从今以后
I won't make you cry anymore
我不会再让你哭了
"Why are you"
"Why are you"
"leave me behind" Just say this now
"leave me behind" 现在才说这种话
"I remember you holding me tight"
"我想起你曾紧抱着我"
"That wonderful night"
"那个美妙的夜晚"
"Stuck in my mind"
"萦绕在我脑海"
"I wanna feel love in your eyes"
"I wanna feel love in your eyes"
"You know me better than I"
"You know me better than I"
"I do"
"I do"
"Love me better love me like you do"
"Love me better love me like you do"
"Thinking back on every moment we spent together"
"回想我们共度的每一刻"
"But scattered all over the place without warning Why"
"却毫无预告地散落一地 Why"
"You know me better than I"
"You know me better than I"
"Don't leave me"
"Don't leave me"
"Can't sleep"
"睡不着觉"
(Preview of next episode) "Thoughts are complicated and the night is long"
(下集预告) "思绪繁杂 长夜漫漫"
Surrounding large residential areas This is the real prime location
大型住宅区的周边 才是真正的黄金地段
(Subscribe for Youguang Apartment) Not only to operate a contractor
(认购有光公寓) 不但要经营承包商
I also want to buy land near the Dugeng area.
还要买下都更区域附近的土地
Everything is according to the instructions of the madam It went smoothly
事情按照夫人的指示 进行得很顺利
Come too, I will send you a wedding invitation
你也来吧 我会寄喜帖给你
He and I have known each other since childhood.
我跟他是从小到大认识的朋友
Inconvenient to handle
不方便处理
Hello, how are you?
喂 你是怎样
Tetsuo, let’s give it a hug.
哲雄 我们抱一下吧
He said he would destroy Tetsuo
他说会毁了哲雄
What is Tetsuo's weakness?
哲雄的弱点是什么
you really can't do that
您真的不可以那样做
Li Douxue
李斗学
where are you going
你到底要去哪里
I need to confirm something
我要去确认一件事
Tetsuo
哲雄
Your biological father...
你的亲生爸爸…